A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of XXX: Correspondence, 1990-1994.
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1990-1994.
  - Secretary of Education.
    - Speech on Choice (Dyke), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Student financial aid programs, 1991. (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - State post secondary review entities, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Substance Abuse and Sexual Assault on College Campuses, Governor's Task Force on, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Violent Crime - Proposed speech, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Virginia Tuition Assistance Grants (TAG), 1990. (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Workforce 2000 - Recommendations, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Education, Dept. of: Anderson v. Wilder, 1990. (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Education, Dept. of: HIV/AIDS Education, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Education, Dept. of: Inappropriate acquisition of computer software, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Education, Dept. of: Reorganization of the Dept. of Education, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Education, Dept. of: Reorganization of the Dept. of Education (JLARC), 1991. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Education, Dept. of: World Class Education Initiative, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1990-1992. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Higher Education in Virginia, State Council on (SCHEV), 1990. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Higher Education in Virginia, State Council on (SCHEV), 1991-1994. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Library and Archives, Virginia State, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Library and Archives, Virginia State, 1991-1993. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Marine Science Museum, Virginia, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Science Museum of Virginia, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - State Education Assistance Authority (SEAA), 1990. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - State Education Assistance Authority (SEAA), 1991-1993. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Education Loan Authority (VELA), 1992. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Bridgeport University, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Longwood College, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Longwood College, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Old Dominion University, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Old Dominion University - Fine Arts addition, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Tidewater Community College, 1992. (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - University of Virginia, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - University of Virginia - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, 1992. (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Virginia State University, 1992 Jan-May. (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Virginia State University, 1992 June-Aug. (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Virginia State University - Emergency Capital Project, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Tech, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - William and Mary, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Advisory Commitee on Girl's Education, 1993 Aug. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Military Institute - All Male Policy, undated. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Appointments to Mary Baldwin College Task Force, 1993 Oct-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Constituent correspondence, 1993 Sept-Oct. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Contracting with private colleges, 1993 Nov. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Draft Plan with Mary Baldwin College, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Estimates of cost of co-education, 1993 Oct. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Excerpts of remarks at commencement, 1990 May 19. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Faulkner v. Jones (Citadel) - Admission of women, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Governor-elect support for VMI / MBC plan, 1993 Nov. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Inaugural parade, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Interview with Governor (single sex education), 1993 June. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Leadership Development Program and Mary Baldwin College, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Military Institute - McFarlane's notes, 1993 Nov 9. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Mary Baldwin College, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Newspaper clippings, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Notes on the plan, 1993 Oct. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Remarks on co-educational remedy, 1993 Sept 25. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Review draft for VMI/MBC plan, 1993 Aug 3. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Review draft of VMI proposal, 1993 Sept 10. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Student Leadership in Three Women's Colleges, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Military Institute - U.S. Dept. of Education Single Sex School Report, 1993 Feb. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Times-Dispatch Poll on Support for Single Sex Education, 1993 Sept 13. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Virginia Women's Institute for Leadership at Mary Baldwin College (Presentation to SCHEV), 1993 Nov. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Military Institute - Wilder endorses Mary Baldwin College Leadership Curriculum, 1993 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Jan-Dec. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Feb. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Feb-Mar. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Mar. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Mar-July. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Mar-Dec. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Mar-1991 Dec. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Apr. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Apr-June. (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 May. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 May-Aug. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 May-1991 Nov. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 June-Oct. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 July-Sept. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Aug-Oct. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Sept-Oct. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Oct. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Oct. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Oct-Nov. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute - United States v. Commonwealth, 1990 Dec. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth - Exhibits, 1990 July. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth - Kearns affidavit, 1990 May. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth - Orders denying the Governor's dismissal, 1990 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth - Orders denying the Governor's dismissal, 1990 Dec. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Jan. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Jan-Feb. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Jan-Feb. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Jan-Apr. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Feb. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Mar. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 June. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Aug-Nov. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1991 Aug-1992 Jan. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth - Court of Appeals for the 4th Circuit, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1992-1993. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1992 Jan. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1992 Apr-May. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1992 Oct. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1992 Oct-1993 June. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Jan-July. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 July-Sept. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Aug. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Sept. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Sept. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Sept. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Sept. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Sept-1994 Jan. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Oct. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Oct. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Nov. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Nov. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Nov. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Military Institute: United States v. Commonwealth, 1993 Dec. (Box 35, Folder 6)